we deserve
death that me and he
that we deserve
death
great SE that's within me than he that's
within the world we
deserve
trity
God Christ the son the Holy
Spirit watching
over
night so thank
you the
chance
we
don't we
don't my
father I am your
son oh holy
spirit through you come and comes to
deliv night so is the go to be like
human die
for
C on thatst
tree we don't deserve to we don't
deserve
to to you we don't deserve to you we
don't deserve we don't deserve we you
deserve we
deserve do I have to die we deserve do I
have
to we
deserve he the
world me than he in the world
that's with me and he the
world that's within me and he the
world the
world that he the world that's what me
that he defend the
world that's me that heend the
world do I have to
die
let
Mr Christ the
Sun a
Di
and we BL the
Trinity we don't deserve
to we don't Des to
Hope we don't deserve to
love we owe it all to
you we
ow
we
we we you
we we
don't we don't